swtor-spy.com 2019-05-21

# Privacy Policy | SWTOR Database

### 1\. Who we are

Swtor-Spy.com is part of [ MMORPG Life](http://www.mmorpg-life.com/) network founded in 2008. This Privacy Policy applies to all of the services and websites offered by Mmorpg-Life.com. To make this notice easy to find, we make it available at the top or at the bottom of all of our pages. 

This policy describes the collection, use, disclosure, retention and protection of your personal information. This notice applies to any website or service which references this Privacy Policy. Where you provide us with your personal information in any of the ways described in section 2 below, you agree that we may collect, store and use it (a) in order to perform our contractual obligations to you, (b) based on our legitimate interest for processing (i.e. for internal administrative purposes or for the detection or prevention of crime) or (c) based on your consent, which you may withdraw at any time, as described in this Privacy Notice. These policy practices may be different than the practices of companies that MMORPG-LIFE.com does not own or control, or of people that MMORPG-LIFE.com does not manage or employ. Please read the following policy to understand how your personal information will be treated as you use our website. 

This policy may change from time to time, so please check back periodically. 

## 2\. What personal data we collect and why we collect it

To the extent permissible under applicable law, we collect information about you and any other party whose details you provide to us when you: 

  * complete online forms (such as post comments or register as a site contributor), enter any competitions or prize draws or participate in any other interactive areas that appear on our website;
  * interact with us using social media;
  * provide your contact details to us when accessing any websites or services we make available or when you update those details; 
  * contact us offline, for example by telephone, email or post.

We also collect information from your devices (including mobile devices) and browsers you use to access and use any of our websites or services (for example, we may collect the device identification number and type, location information and connection information such as statistics on your page views, traffic to and from the sites, referral URL, ad data, and your IP address). We may do this using cookies or similar technologies. This is done for our own internal administrative purposes and detection or prevention of malicious behavior or crime. 

If you intend giving us personal information about someone else, you are responsible for ensuring that you comply with any obligation and consent obligations under applicable data protections laws. In so far as required by applicable data protection laws, you must ensure that beforehand you have their explicit consent to do so and that you explain to them how we collect, use, disclose and retain their personal information or direct them to read our Privacy Notice.

### 2a. Comments

When visitors leave comments on the site we collect the data shown in the comments form, and also the visitor’s IP address and browser user agent string to help spam detection.

An anonymized string created from your email address (also called a hash) may be provided to the Gravatar service to see if you are using it. The Gravatar service privacy policy is available here: <https://automattic.com/privacy/>. After approval of your comment, your profile picture is visible to the public in the context of your comment.

###  2b. Cookies and Traffic Data

If you leave a comment on our site you may opt-in to saving your name, email address and website in cookies. These are for your convenience so that you do not have to fill in your details again when you leave another comment. These cookies will last for one year.

If you have an account and you log in to this site, we will set a temporary cookie to determine if your browser accepts cookies. This cookie contains no personal data and is discarded when you close your browser.

When you log in, we will also set up several cookies to save your login information and your screen display choices. Login cookies last for two days, and screen options cookies last for a year. If you select “Remember Me”, your login will persist for two weeks. If you log out of your account, the login cookies will be removed.

If you edit or publish an article, an additional cookie will be saved in your browser. This cookie includes no personal data and simply indicates the post ID of the article you just edited. It expires after 1 day.

Targeting or advertising cookies are used to deliver adverts more relevant to you and your interests. They are also used to limit the number of times you see an advertisement as well as help measure the effectiveness of the advertising campaign. They are usually placed by advertisers, advertising agencies or ad servicing technologies. They remember that you have visited a website and this information is shared with other organizations such as advertisers.

There are cookies that are stored for the purpose of Analytics. More detailed explanation of which Third Party services we use and how to opt out of data tracking through cookies these services create are described in section 3.

We keep a record of traffic data which is logged automatically by our servers (both our web site servers and our ad serving technologies), such as your Internet Protocol (IP) address, device information, the website that you visited before ours and the website you visit after leaving our site. We also collect some site and service statistics such as access rates and page views. We are not able to identify any individual from traffic data or site statistics.

You may be able to configure your browser or our website or the websites of our partners to restrict cookies or block all cookies if you wish, however if you disable cookies you may find this affects your ability to use certain parts of our website, or services. For more information about cookies and instructions on how to adjust your browser settings to accept, delete or reject cookies, see the [www.youronlinechoices.co.uk](http://www.youronlinechoices.co.uk/) website. 

## 3\. Analytics

Analytics are intended to help us understand how visitors use our website to help improve our services. We use third party tools that create cookies and store necessary technical information. To opt-out of Google Analytics storing data in cookies when you visit our website please [visit this page](https://support.google.com/analytics/answer/181881). We also use Alexa Certified Site Metrics for analytical purposes.[Click here to opt out of Alexa Certified Site Metrics.](https://www.alexa.com/certifyoptout)

## 4\. Embedded content from other websites

Articles on this site may include embedded content (e.g. videos, images, articles, etc.). Embedded content from other websites behaves in the exact same way as if the visitor has visited the other website.

These websites may collect data about you, use cookies, embed additional third-party tracking, and monitor your interaction with that embedded content, including tracing your interaction with the embedded content if you have an account and are logged in to that website.

## 5\. Sharing your information

We may share your information with: 

  * third parties which process information on our behalf (e.g. internet service and platform providers, advertising agencies, agency trading desks, supply side platforms and data management platforms) so that they may help us to provide you with the products, services and information you have requested or which we believe is of interest to you;
  * partners, including website and mobile app publishers, resellers and developers that may help us to provide you with the products, services and information you have requested or which we believe is of interest to you;
  * third parties where you have a relationship with that third party and you have consented to us sending information (for example social media sites or other third party application providers);
  * third parties for marketing purposes (e.g. our partners and other third parties with whom we work and whose products or services we think will interest you);
  * law enforcement agencies so that they may detect or prevent crime or prosecute offenders;
  * any third party in the context of actual or threatened legal proceedings, provided we can do so lawfully (for example in response to a court order);
  * another organization if we sell or buy (or negotiate to sell or buy) any business or assets;
  * another organization to whom we may transfer our agreement with you; and
  * Government departments where reporting is mandatory under applicable law.

We may share non-personally identifiable information about the use of our website, applications, products or services publicly or with third parties but this will not include information that can be used to identify you. 

## 6\. Your information and your rights

If you are based within the EEA or within another jurisdiction having similar data protection laws, in certain circumstances you have the following rights: 

  * the right to be told how we use your information and obtain access to your information;
  * the right to have your information rectified or erased or place restrictions on processing your information;
  * the right to object to the processing of your information e.g. for direct marketing purposes;
  * the right to have any information you provided to us on an automated basis returned to you in a structured, commonly used and machine-readable format, or sent directly to another company, where technically feasible (“data portability”);
  * where the processing of your information is based on your consent, the right to withdraw that consent subject to legal or contractual restrictions;
  * the right to object to any decisions based on the automated processing of your personal data, including profiling; and
  * the right to lodge a complaint with the supervisory authority responsible for data protection matters.

If you have an account on this site, or have left comments, you can request to receive an exported file of the personal data we hold about you, including any data you have provided to us. You can also request that we erase any personal data we hold about you. This does not include any data we are obliged to keep for administrative, legal, or security purposes.

If you withdraw your consent to the use of your personal information for purposes set out in our Privacy Policy, we may not be able to provide you with access to all or parts of our website and services.

We will retain your personal information for the duration of our business relationship and afterwards for as long as is necessary and relevant for our legitimate business purposes, in accordance with our data retention, marking and destruction policy or as otherwise permitted applicable laws and regulation. Where we no longer need your personal information, we will dispose of it in a secure manner (without further notice to you).

## 7\. Security and storage of information

We will keep your information secure by taking appropriate technical and organisational measures against its unauthorised or unlawful processing and against its accidental loss, destruction or damage. We will do our best to protect your personal information but we cannot guarantee the security of your information which is transmitted to our website or services or to other website, applications and services via an internet or similar connection. If we have given you (or you have chosen) a password to access certain areas of our websites or services please keep this password safe – we will not share this password with anyone. 

If you believe your account has been compromised, please contact us at privacy@mmorpg-life.com. 

## 8\. Transfers outside of the European Economic Area

Personal information in the European Union is protected by data protection laws but other countries do not necessarily protect your personal information in the same way. 

Our website and some of our applications or services or parts of them may also be hosted in the United States or otherwise outside of the EEA (which means all the EU countries plus Norway, Iceland and Liechtenstein) (“EEA”) and this means that we may transfer any information which is submitted by you through the website or the application or service outside the EEA to the United States or to other territories outside of the EEA. When you send an email to us, this will also be stored on email servers which are hosted in the United States and therefore may be outside of the EEA. 

We may use service providers based outside of the EEA to help us provide our website and services to you and this means that we may transfer your information to service providers outside the EEA for the purpose of providing our advertising and services to you. 

We take steps to ensure that where your information is transferred outside of the EEA by our service providers and hosting providers, appropriate measures and controls are in place to protect that information in accordance with applicable data protection laws and regulations. In each case, such transfers are made in accordance with the requirements of Regulations (EU) 2016/679 (the General Data Protection Regulations or “GDPR”) and may be based on the use of the European Commission’s Standard Model Clauses for transfers of personal data outside the EEA. 

By using our website, products or services or by interacting with us in the ways described in this Privacy Notice, you consent to the transfer of your information outside the EEA in the circumstances set out in this Privacy Notice. If you do not want your information to be transferred outside the EEA you should not use our website, applications or services. 

## 9\. Further information

If you have any queries about how we treat your information, the contents of this notice, your rights under local law, how to update your records or how to obtain a copy of the information that we hold about you, please write to our Data Protection Officer at MMORPG Life, Ljube Didica 1, 11000 Belgrade, Serbia or send an email to privacy@mmorpg-life.com 

Updated: May 25th, 2018.
